iranmania.com 2004-04-02

# IranMania Privacy Statement

IranManiaTM  
**www.iranmania.com م1999-2003 Persicom Ltd**

**Privacy Statement for IranMania**

Persicom Ltd has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this web site: IranMania. This site contains links to other sites. IranMania is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

**Information gathered**

We limit the information we collect about customers to what is needed to accurately provide products and services. When we index the web, we look first for all publicly available web sites and information within those web sites. Information gathered relates to the content of those web sites.

Occasionally we ask you to provide us information such as your name and email address. You never have to answer these questions although this may limit what services we can offer. This information will not be used unless otherwise stated but may occasionally be used to send you email communications to provide information which we think you will find useful, including information about new products and services from IranMania.

It is our policy only to send email to customers who give us permission to do so. In every such email, we will also have instructions on how to unsubscribe so that you will not receive any future emails from IranMania if you do not wish to. see the "Opt-out Policy " below.

IranMania will never disclose individually identifiable information about its customers to any third party without first receiving that customer's permission.

**Third Party Advertising**

Some of the ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to you by DoubleClick, our Web advertising partner. Information about your visit to this site, such as number of times you have viewed an ad (but not your name, address, or other personal information), is used to serve ads to you on this site.

For more information about DoubleClick, cookies, and how to "opt-out", [ please click here.](http://www.doubleclick.net/us/corporate/privacy)

**Third Party Cookies**

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.

**Opt-Out Policy**

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request information about the visitor.

You can tell us if you don't want to be listed in any of the IranMania sections. You can tell us if you don't want to receive communication from IranMania such as email newsletters announcing products or new features. And, of course, you can always decline to provide the personal information to us in the first place.

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service.

You can send email to [General feedback](http://www.iranmania.com/contacts/)

**Correct/Update**

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided.

Email [General feedback](http://www.iranmania.com/contacts/)

**Contacting the Web Site**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact

IranMania System Administrator  

**م** ** 1999-2003 Persicom Limited - All rights reserved**
